Guide to the From Shore to Shore Records AIA.095
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
From Shore to Shore Records
1973-2014
1988-1994
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Mullins, Patrick J., 1952-
AIA.095
7.17 Linear Feet in 11 manuscript boxes, 1 record carton, and 2 media boxes
4 Betacam_SP
88 Betacam
2 U-matic
2 D-2
1 Digital_Betacam
1 Quarter_Inch_Audio_Reel
2 audiocassettes
4 DAT
74 MiniDV
1 1_Inch_Video_Reel
1 16mm_film_reels
241.1 Megabytes in 3 computer files
From Shore to Shore: Irish Traditional Music in New York City is a 2006 documentary created by filmmaker Patrick Mullins. The film documents the Irish traditional music scene in the greater New York City area in the late 20th century by focusing on the experiences of Irish musicians who emigrated to the United States, as well as the lives of their children, many of whom continued practicing their musical heritage as Irish Americans. From Shore to Shore makes use of oral histories and interviews to demonstrate the importance of family and community in shaping Irish American culture, with a particular emphasis on traditional music and dance. The From Shore to Shore Records (dated 1973-2014, bulk 1988-1994) consists of materials created and collected by Mullins in the course of making the documentary film. Materials consist of paper production files that include research materials, logs, and correspondence regarding licensing, distribution, and reproduction permissions; as well as audio, video, and film elements in various formats. These recordings include interviews, performances, festival and fleadh footage, B-roll footage, and final edits.
Scope and Contents
The From Shore to Shore Records (dated 1973-2014, bulk 1988-1994) consists of materials created and collected by filmmaker Patrick Mullins in the course of making the documentary film. Materials consist of paper production files that include research materials, logs, and correspondence regarding licensing, distribution, and reproduction permissions; as well as audio, video, and film elements in various formats. These recordings include interviews, performances, festival and fleadh footage, B-roll footage, and final edits.
Appraisal
MiniDV backups (stored in Boxes 13-14) of Betacam recordings have been temporarily retained until reformatting of originals is successful.
Arrangement
Materials are in two series:
Series I. Recordings
Series II. Production Research and Documentation
This collection has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Patrick Mullins in June 2025; the accession number associated with this gift is 2025.065.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Born-Digital Access Policies and Procedures
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted. An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Historical Note
From Shore to Shore: Irish Traditional Music in New York City is a 2006 documentary created by filmmaker Patrick Mullins. The film documents the Irish traditional music scene in the greater New York City area in the late 20th century by focusing on the experiences of Irish musicians who emigrated to the United States, as well as the lives of their children, many of whom continued practicing their musical heritage as Irish Americans. From Shore to Shore makes use of oral histories and interviews to demonstrate the importance of family and community in shaping Irish American culture, with a particular emphasis on traditional music and dance. Production of the film began in April 1988 when Mullins began recording interviews and taping performances at festivals. The film has been broadcast on PBS and is accessible online at Folkstreams.
Existence and Location of Copies
Shore to Shore: Irish Traditional Music in New York City is accessible through Folkstreams at https://www.folkstreams.net/films/from-shore-to-shore.
Irish Americans -- Music.; Irish Americans.; Irish Americans -- New York (N.Y.); Folk music.; Irish Americans -- Interviews; Documentary films; Mullins, Patrick J., 1952-
- Series I. Recordings, 1988-1999; 6.96 Linear Feet in 8 manuscript boxes, 1 record carton, and 2 media boxes; 241.1 Megabytes in 3 computer files; 4 Betacam_SP; 88 Betacam; 2 U-matic; 2 D-2; 1 Digital_Betacam; 1 Quarter_Inch_Audio_Reel; 2 audiocassettes; 4 DAT; 74 MiniDV; 1 1_Inch_Video_Reel; 1 16mm_film_reels
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of audio, video, and film recordings created in the production of From Shore to Shore. Materials in this series include interviews with traditional Irish and Irish American performers, including Dan Collins, Brian Conway, Tom Doherty, Mary Coleman Hannon, Earle Hitchner, Maureen Doherty Macken, Andy McGann, Mary Coleman O'Beirne, Paddy Reynolds, and Martin Wynne. The series includes recordings of performances at music festivals and fleadhs, many of which are from the Snug Harbor Irish Traditional Music Festival, as well as recordings of pub sessiuns and parties.
  - Irish Arts Center -- John Whelan, Eileen Ivers, Jerry O'Sullivan, 1988-04-12; cuid44486
    - Tape 02, cuid44487 (Box 1, Betacam cuid44487)
    - Tape 03, cuid44488 (Box 1, Betacam cuid44488)
  - Irish Arts Center -- John Whelan Interview, 1988-04-12; cuid44489
    - Tape 04, cuid44490 (Box 1, Betacam cuid44490)
    - Tape 05, cuid44491 (Box 1, Betacam cuid44491)
  - Irish Arts Center -- Eileen Ivers Interview, 1988-04-12; cuid44492
    - Tape 06, cuid44493 (Box 1, Betacam cuid44493)
    - Tape 07, cuid44494 (Box 1, Betacam cuid44494)
  - Tom and Betty Doolan House Party, Glenrock, New Jersey -- Various Performances and Interviews, Including John Morrison, Tom Doolan, Jerry O'Sullivan, Joanie Madden, Joe Kelly, Willie Kelly, John Whelan, Louise Whelan, Eileen Ivers, Mick Kenny (Dublin), Earle Hitchner (Interview), 1988-04-17; cuid44495 (Box 1, Betacam cuid44495)
  - Tom and Betty Doolan House Party, Glenrock, New Jersey -- Various Performances and Interviews, 1988-04-17; cuid44496 (Box 1, Betacam cuid44496)
  - Tom and Betty Doolan House Party, Glenrock, New Jersey -- Jerry O'Sullivan Interview, 1988-04-17; cuid44497
    - Part 1, cuid44498 (Box 1, Betacam cuid44498)
    - Part 2, cuid44499 (Box 1, Betacam cuid44499)
  - Tom and Betty Doolan House Party, Glenrock, New Jersey -- Various Performances and Interviews, 1988-04-17; cuid44500 (Box 1, Betacam cuid44500)
  - Tom and Betty Doolan House Party, Glenrock, New Jersey -- Various Performances and Interviews, 1988-04-17; cuid44501 (Box 2, Betacam cuid44501)
  - Tom and Betty Doolan House Party, Glenrock, New Jersey -- Various Performances and Earle Hitchner Interview, 1988-04-17; cuid44502 (Box 2, Betacam cuid44502)
  - Tom and Betty Doolan House Party, Glenrock, New Jersey -- Musicians and Album Cover Photos, 1988-04-17; cuid44503 (Box 2, Betacam cuid44503)
  - Snug Harbor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Brian Conway, Martin Wynne Fiddle Workshop, 1988-06-25; cuid44504
    - Tape A1, cuid44505 (Box 2, Betacam cuid44505)
    - Tape A2, cuid44506 (Box 2, Betacam cuid44506)
  - Snug Harbor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Fiddle Convention: Martin Wynne, Paddy Reynolds (Led by Allan Feldman), 1988-06-25; cuid44507 (Box 2, Betacam cuid44507)
  - Snug Harbor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Paddy Reynolds ("Fiddlers' Convention"), Crowd Shots, 1988-06-25; cuid44508 (Box 2, Betacam cuid44508)
  - Snug Harbor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Martin Wynne, Maureen Glynn / Women in Irish Music: Mary Bergin, Rita Flaherty, Jane Kelton, Maureen Doherty, Antoinette McKenna (led by Janis Benincasa), 1988-06-25; cuid44509 (Box 2, Betacam cuid44509)
  - Snug Harbor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Women in Irish Music, 1988-06-25; cuid44510 (Box 2, Betacam cuid44510)
  - Snug Harbor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Brian Conway, Paddy O'Brien, Felix Dolan (Main Stage), Robbie O'Connell, 1988-06-25; cuid44511 (Box 2, Betacam cuid44511)
  - Snug Harbor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Robbie O'Connell, Tom and Maureen Doherty, Paddy Reynolds, Felix Dolan (Main Stage), 1988-06-25; cuid44512 (Box 2, Betacam cuid44512)
  - Snug Harbor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Tom and Maureen Doherty, Paddy Reynolds, Felix Dolan (Main Stage), Paddy O'Brien at Eagle Tavern, 1988-06-25; cuid44513 (Box 3, Betacam cuid44513)
  - Snug Harbor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Martin Wynne, Brian Conway, 1988-06-25; cuid44514 (Box 3, Betacam cuid44514)
  - Snug Harbor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Paddy Reynolds ("Fiddlers' Convention"), 1988-06-25; cuid44515 (Box 3, Betacam cuid44515)
  - Snug Harbor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Martin Wynne, Maureen Glynn, 1988-06-25; cuid44516 (Box 3, Betacam cuid44516)
  - Snug Harbor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Women in Irish Music: Mary Bergin, Rita Flaherty, Jane Kelton, Maureen Doherty, 1988-06-25; cuid44517 (Box 3, Betacam cuid44517)
  - Snug Harbor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Brian Conway, Paddy O'Brien, Felix Dolan (Main Stage), Ceili Dance Area (Sunset), 1988-06-25; cuid44518 (Box 3, Betacam cuid44518)
  - Snug Harbor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Ceili Dance Area (Sunet), Robbie O'Connell, Tom and Maureen Doherty, Paddy Reynolds, Felix Dolan (Main Stage), 1988-06-25; cuid44519 (Box 3, Betacam cuid44519)
  - Snug Harbor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Tom and Maureen Doherty, Paddy Reynolds, Felix Dolan (Main Stage), Paddy O'Brien at Eagle Tavern, 1988-06-25; cuid44520 (Box 3, Betacam cuid44520)
  - Snug Habor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Eagle Tavern Session, Dancing, 1988-06-25; cuid44521 (Box 3, Betacam cuid44521)
  - Snug Harbor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Selects -- Mattie Connolly, Rita Flaherty, Tom Doherty, Donny Golden, June 1988; TW_AIA_095_ER_1
  - Eagle Tavern Concert -- Andy McGann, Brian Conway, Felix Dolan, 1988-10-08; cuid44522
    - Music Set 1, cuid44523 (Box 3, Betacam cuid44523)
    - Music Set 1, cuid44524 (Box 4, Betacam cuid44524)
    - Music Sets 1 and 2, cuid44525 (Box 3, Betacam cuid44525)
    - Music Sets 1 and 2, cuid44526 (Box 4, Betacam cuid44526)
    - Music Set 2, cuid44527 (Box 4, Betacam cuid44527)
    - Music Set 2, cuid44528 (Box 4, Betacam cuid44528)
  - Martin Wynne's Apartment, Bronx, New York -- Martin and Vincent Harrison Play and Talk, 1988-10-08; cuid44529 (Box 4, Betacam cuid44529)
  - Martin Wynne's Apartment, Bronx, New York -- Martin, Vincent Harrison, and Becky Miller Play and Talk, 1988-10-08; cuid44530 (Box 4, Betacam cuid44530)
  - Martin Wynne's Apartment, Bronx, New York -- Martin, Vincent Harrison, and Becky Miller Play and Talk; Martin Wynne Interview, 1988-10-08; cuid44531 (Box 4, Betacam cuid44531)
  - Martin Wynne's Apartment, Bronx, New York -- Martin Interview; With Music Notebooks, 1988-10-08; cuid44532 (Box 4, Betacam cuid44532)
  - Album Cover Photos, undated; cuid44533 (Box 4, Betacam cuid44533)
  - Eagle Tavern -- Andy McGann Interview 1, 1988-10-08; cuid44534 (Box 4, Betacam cuid44534)
  - Tom Doherty at Home, Bay Ridge, Brooklyn -- Interview and Performance, 1989-02-24; cuid44535
    - Part 1, cuid44536 (Box 4, Betacam cuid44536)
    - Part 2, cuid44537 (Box 5, Betacam cuid44537)
  - Paddy Reynolds at Home -- Interview and Performance, 1989-02-24; cuid44538
    - Part 1, cuid44539 (Box 5, Betacam cuid44539)
    - Part 2, cuid44540 (Box 5, Betacam cuid44540)
    - Part 3, cuid44541 (Box 5, Betacam cuid44541)
  - The Celts Rise Again Concert, Bottom Line, New York City, 1989-02-24; cuid44542
    - Jerry O'Sullivan and James Keane, Mick Moloney, Altan, cuid44543 (Box 5, Betacam cuid44543)
    - Altan, Fresh Takes, Patrick Street, cuid44544 (Box 5, Betacam cuid44544)
    - Patrick Street, Liz Carroll, Dáithí Sproule, cuid44545 (Box 5, Betacam cuid44545)
    - Andy M. Steward and Manus Lunny, Johnny Cunningham and fiddle jam, cuid44546 (Box 5, Betacam cuid44546)
    - Greenfields of America, cuid44547 (Box 5, Betacam cuid44547)
    - Greenfields of America, Mick Moloney Backstage Interview, cuid44548 (Box 5, Betacam cuid44548)
  - New York Fleadh Cheoil, Manhattan College, Bronx, New York -- Various Competitions and Performances, Maureen Glynn Students, Brendan Bulger, 1989-05-07; cuid44549 (Box 5, Betacam cuid44549)
  - New York Fleadh Cheoil, Manhattan College, Bronx, New York -- Various Competitions and Performances, Brendan Bulger, 1988-05-07; cuid44550 (Box 6, Betacam cuid44550)
  - New York Fleadh Cheoil, Manhattan College, Bronx, New York -- Various Competitions and Performances, Marie Reilly and Others, 1988-05-07; cuid44551 (Box 6, Betacam cuid44551)
  - New York Fleadh Cheoil, Manhattan College, Bronx, New York -- Senior Competitions and Performances: Buddy Connoly and John Vesey, Maureen Glynn and Billy McComiskey Judging, Joanie Madden and Eileen Ivers, Jerry O'Sullivan and John Whelan, 1988-05-07; cuid44552 (Box 6, Betacam cuid44552)
  - New York Fleadh Cheoil, Manhattan College, Bronx, New York -- Various Competitions and Performances, John Whelan and Jerry O'Sullivan, Pat Conway Interview, 1988-05-07; cuid44553 (Box 6, Betacam cuid44553)
  - New York Fleadh Cheoil, Manhattan College, Bronx, New York -- Pat Conway Interview, Maureen Glynn Interview, 1988-05-07; cuid44554 (Box 6, Betacam cuid44554)
  - New York Fleadh Cheoil, Manhattan College, Bronx, New York -- Maureen Glynn Interview, 1988-05-07; cuid44555 (Box 6, Betacam cuid44555)
  - New York Fleadh Cheoil, Manhattan College, Bronx, New York -- Milltown Lounge Pub Session with Dancing, 1988-05-07; cuid44556 (Box 6, Betacam cuid44556)
  - Snug Habor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Brian Conway Interview, The Wednesday Nighters, Step Dance Workshop with Maureen Glynn, 1989-06-24; cuid44557 (Box 6, Betacam cuid44557)
  - Snug Habor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Step Dance Workshop, Sean nos: Mairéad Ní Mhaonaigh, Treasa O'Carroll, Father Charlie Coen, 1989-06-24; cuid44558 (Box 6, Betacam cuid44558)
  - Snug Harbor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Sean nos: Faither Charlie Coen, Mairéad Ní Mhaonaigh, Treasa O'Carroll; Uilleann Pipes: Matty Connolly and Bill Ochs, 1989-06-24; cuid44559 (Box 6, Betacam cuid44559)
  - Snug Habor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Fiddle Convention Duets: Brian Conway and Tony DeMarco, Andy McGann and Paddy Reynolds (led by Allan Feldman), 1989-06-24; cuid44560 (Box 6, Betacam cuid44560)
  - Snug Habor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Step Dance Demonstrations; Main Stage Performances: Maureen Glynn, Linda Hickman and Tony DeMarco, Robbie O'Connell; Dan Collins Interview Part 1, 1989-06-24; cuid44561 (Box 7, Betacam cuid44561)
  - Snug Harbor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Dan Collins Interview Part 2, 1989-06-24; cuid44562 (Box 7, Betacam cuid44562)
  - Snug Habor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- Dan Collins Interview Part 3, 1989-06-24; cuid44563 (Box 7, Betacam cuid44563)
  - Snug Habor Irish Traditional Music Festival -- McGoverns Pub, Woodside, Queens: Brian Conway, James Keane, Victor Cunneen, 1989-06-24; cuid44564 (Box 7, Betacam cuid44564)
  - New York City Exteriors -- Lower Manhattan Skyline, Irish Arts Center, West 53rd Street, 1990-11-18; cuid44565 (Box 7, Betacam cuid44565)
  - O'Beirne Home, Woodside Queens -- James O'Beirne Interview Part 1, 1990-11-18; cuid44566 (Box 7, Betacam cuid44566)
  - James O'Beirne Interview Part 2; Andy McGann Interview Part 1, 1990-11-18; cuid44567 (Box 7, Betacam cuid44567)
  - Andy McGann Interview Part 2, 1990-11-18; cuid44568 (Box 7, Betacam cuid44568)
  - Andy McGann Interview Part 3; Mary Coleman O'Beirne and Mary Coleman Hannon Interview Part 1, 1990-11-18; cuid44569 (Box 7, Betacam cuid44569)
  - Mary Coleman O'Beirne and Mary Coleman Hannon Interview Part 2; James O'Beirne and Andy McGann Play, 1990-11-18; cuid44570 (Box 7, Betacam cuid44570)
  - B-Roll -- O'Beirne Family Photos; Homemade 78 RPM Disc by Lad O'Beirne, 1990-11-18; cuid44571 (Box 7, Betacam cuid44571)
  - Martin Wynne's Apartment, Bronx, New York -- Martin Interview and Performance, 1990-12-27; cuid44572
    - Part 1, cuid44573 (Box 8, Betacam cuid44573)
    - Part 2, cuid44574 (Box 8, Betacam cuid44574)
    - Part 3, cuid44575 (Box 8, Betacam cuid44575)
  - Martin Wynn Plays (Part 4); Maureen Doherty and Johnny Cronin Play, Bayside, Queens, 1990-12-27; cuid44576 (Box 8, Betacam cuid44576)
  - Maureen Glynn Interview 2, Bayside, Queens Home, 1990-12-27; cuid44577
    - Part 1, cuid44578 (Box 8, Betacam cuid44578)
    - Part 2, cuid44579 (Box 8, Betacam cuid44579)
  - Maureen Doherty Interview, Bayside, Queens, 1990-12-27; cuid44580 (Box 8, Betacam cuid44580)
  - B-Roll -- New York City Exteriors -- Glocca Morra Pub, Bainbridge Avenue, Manhattan Skyline, Evening, 1991-06-07; cuid44581 (Box 8, Betacam cuid44581)
  - B-Roll -- New York City Exteriors -- Manhattan Skyline, Evening, 1991-06-07; cuid44582 (Box 8, Betacam cuid44582)
  - Animated Stills, undated; cuid44583
    - Tape C4/S4, cuid44584 (Box 8, Betacam cuid44584)
    - Tape E7/S1, cuid44585 (Box 8, Betacam cuid44585)
  - New York City B-Roll -- Woodside, Queens Street Scenes, circa October 1989; cuid44586
    - Tape K1, cuid44587 (Box 9, U-matic cuid44587)
    - Tape K2, cuid44588 (Box 9, U-matic cuid44588)
  - From Shore to Shore: Irish Traditional Music in New York City -- Original Recordings, cuid44589
    - Retrospective Reels (Folkstreems), circa 1993; cuid44590 (Box 9, Digital betacam cuid44590)
    - Digital Clone, Final Edited Master, 1993-11-09; cuid44591 (Box 9, D-2 cuid44591)
    - Digital Clone, Final Edited Master No Titles, 1993-11-08; cuid44592 (Box 9, D-2 cuid44592)
    - Final Edited Master, 1993-11-08; cuid44593 (Box 9, 1 inch video reel cuid44593)
  - John Glynn Home Movies, undated; cuid44594
    - Reels 1 and 2, cuid44595 (Box 9, Betacam sp cuid44595)
    - Reel 3, cuid44596 (Box 9, Betacam sp cuid44596)
  - Audio Selects Reel -- Gabriel Donohue, Eileen Ivers, Joanie Madden; New York Ceili Band; Lad O'Beirne and Michael Coleman; Louis Quinn; Andy McGann and Paddy Reynolds; John Whelan et al., undated; cuid44597 (Box 9, Betacam sp cuid44597)
  - Archival and Stock Footage Film Compilation, undated; cuid44598 (Box 9, Betacam sp cuid44598)
  - "Incidental Music" -- Gabriel Donahue, Eileen Ivers, Joanie Madden, 1991-01-23; cuid44599 (Box 9, Quarter inch audio reel cuid44599)
  - Lad O'Beirne Disc Recordings, undated; cuid44600 (Box Shared Tamiment 202, Audiocassette cuid44600)
  - Lad O'Beirne and Michael Coleman -- "Lady of the Island" and "The Flowery Fields of Scotland", undated; cuid44601 (Box Shared Tamiment 202, Audiocassette cuid44601)
  - Final Interviews, 1992-07-30-1992-08-05; cuid44602
    - Tape 1, cuid44603 (Box Shared Tamiment 202, Dat cuid44603)
    - Tape 2, cuid44604 (Box Shared Tamiment 202, Dat cuid44604)
    - Tape 3, cuid44605 (Box Shared Tamiment 202, Dat cuid44605)
  - Tape I-2 -- New York Ceili Band; Lad O'Beirne; Lad O'Beirne and Michael Coleman, 1973-2014; cuid44606 (Box Shared Tamiment 202, Minidv cuid44606)
  - Final Narration by Jerry O'Sullivan, 1993-10-11; cuid44607 (Box Shared Tamiment 202, Dat cuid44607)
  - Maureen Glynn Tribute, 1999-03-05; cuid44608
    - Tape 1, cuid44609 (Box Shared Tamiment 202, Minidv cuid44609)
    - Tape 2, cuid44610 (Box Shared Tamiment 202, Minidv cuid44610)
    - Tape 3, cuid44611 (Box Shared Tamiment 202, Minidv cuid44611)
    - Tape 4, cuid44612 (Box Shared Tamiment 202, Minidv cuid44612)
  - B-Roll -- New York City; Archival 78 RPM Discs and Phonographs; St. Patrick's Day Parade, undated; cuid44613 (Box Shared Tamiment 170, 16mm film reels cuid44613)
- Series II. Production Research and Documentation, 1973-2014; 1.31 Linear Feet in 3 manuscript boxes
  This series consists of research and production documentation, including correspondence, ephemera, logs, clippings, and photographs. These materials document research activities, funding, licensing and distribution, and publicity.
  - Video Logs, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
  - Library of Congress Registrations, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Funding and Budgets, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Releases, Permissions, Agreements, 1988-1993 (Box 10, Folder 7-8)
  - Film Selects (16mm), 1993 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Publicity, 1989-2011 (Box 10, Folder 10-13)
  - WNET Channel 13, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Narration, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Licensing and Distribution, 1992-2011 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Transcription, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Permissions for Reproduction, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Music Cue Sheet, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Video Cover (VHS), 1989-1993 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Graphics, 1988-1999 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Photo Licensing and Permissions, 1989-1993 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Archive Films, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Broadcast Correspondence -- Rejection Letters, 1992-1995 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence Post-Completion, 1989-2011 (Box 11, Folder 12-13)
  - Cherish the Ladies, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Colorlab, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - TipArm Agreement, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - CRC Royalties, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Sing Out!, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - NEA -- Folk Arts, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Photo Research, 1990-1993 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Photographs, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 21-23, Box 12, Folder 1-4)